{
    "subject": "resource/Snje\u017eana_Kordi\u0107",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Osijek",
    "human_readable": "Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 was born in Osijek.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.940189778804779,
            "question": "Where was Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9008712768554688,
            "question": "What year was Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6932098865509033,
            "question": "What is Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49354514479637146,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45497268438339233,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Osijek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4496563971042633,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Osijek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4022427201271057,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Osijek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3673713505268097,
            "question": "Is Osijek a city in Croatia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32815611362457275,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0955934077501297,
            "question": "What is the significance of birthplaces?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 was born in Osijek.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8065_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can we learn more about Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8065_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Osijek a city in Croatia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8065_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Osijek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8065_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8065_48.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain information about Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107, including her birthplace. In one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8065/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt), it is mentioned that \"Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 was born on October 29, 1964, in Osijek, County of Osijek-Baranja, Croatia.\" This supports the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 was born on October 29, 1964, in Osijek, County of Osijek-Baranja, Croatia,\" which supports the statement that Snje\u017eana Kordi\u0107 was born in Osijek."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}